chinatraderonline.com 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy - China Trader Online

**YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS**

The following policy explains our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**Information Collected**

1.  Your Personally Identifiable Information Collected by Chinatraderonline.com

When you register as a new user with the Chinatraderonline.com Web site (the “Site”), our registration form may require you to give us certain information such as your first and last name, email address, date of birth, and zip code. Chinatraderonline.com will also collect other information you volunteer to us through use of our service that can identify you as a specific individual. We refer to this information as Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”). You may always choose not to provide PII, however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service or particular information. We may also collect demographic and other data, which may include PII, generally through surveys and forms which you may or may not choose to participate in. If you place an order for goods on Chinatraderonline.com or through a Chinatraderonline.com Partner, you may be required to enter your credit card number and information, as well as your shipping address and/or other contact information.

Reviews of products ideas and merchants will display PII of those users who have posted such reviews, as will public products lists. The PII displayed on user postings will be limited to first name and initial of last name.

2\. products Recipients’ Personally Identifiable Information Added by Users

Once registered, a user will be able to create profiles for friends and family or any other products recipients. In order to save such profiles in an account, the user will be required to enter some PII for the products recipient such as the products recipient’s name, birth date, gender, and their relationship to the user. This information is stored on the My products Lists and Saved Profiles area of the user’s Chinatraderonline.com account. As such, any user should obtain the consent of other individuals prior to entering their information on the Site. Chinatraderonline.com respects the privacy of the products recipients entered into our system and will not share any PII of products recipients with third parties other than for the purposes enumerated under Use of products Recipient’s Personally Identifiable Information by Chinatraderonline.com below.

3\. Personally Identifiable Information Collected by Chinatraderonline.com Business Partners

Chinatraderonline.com works with third-party advertising companies, sponsors and other companies with whom we do business (“Business Partners”) to place advertising on our site and in email communications sent to our registered users and other communications related to the Chinatraderonline.com service. In order to complete a transaction, Business Partners may collect PII of a products recipient on their respective Web site. Such collection of PII is governed by that Business Partner’s privacy policy. 

Chinatraderonline.com may correlate or match registered users' information, including PII, with information held by our Business Partners to target ads or otherwise improve the effectiveness of our service. Our Business Partners may read or set cookies on your hard drive, use pixel tags, track which ads you have viewed, or collect other information about you.

From time to time, Chinatraderonline.com may also have special offers or promotions that are sponsored by a Business Partner. In order to participate in these offers, you may be required to follow a separate registration process. If you consent to receive information from a Business Partner through an opt-in or opt-out process Chinatraderonline.com may pass your information to such Business Partner.

Chinatraderonline.com may also offer goods or services for purchase available by our Business Partners by way of email communications to our users. If you purchase goods or services offered through Chinatraderonline.com by a Business Partner, then you may be required to submit PII in order to complete the transaction and Chinatraderonline.com may provide your PII to such Business Partner for that purpose.

In some cases, we may enter into a promotional relationship with a Business Partner in which we prominently display their brand name or trademarks on pages that appear the same as or very similar to the pages of the Chinatraderonline.com service. These pages are known as "Co-Branded Pages" and these particular Business Partners are known as “Co-Branded Business Partners.” If the page on which you submit information is a Co-Branded Page, or was accessed by clicking on a link on a Co-Branded Page, then we may share your personal information with the associated Co-Branded Business Partner. Co-Branded Business Partners may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. Chinatraderonline.com disclaims all liability for the privacy policies and procedures on any Business Partner or Co-Branded Business Partner Web site. You will need to contact the Co-Branded Business Partner to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such Co-Branded Business Partners in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us (see Use of your PII by Business Partners below). 

We currently contract with a third party to help to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we may use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The information we collect through these Web beacons or cookies is non-personally identifiable and includes the pages, the links you click on and where you came from. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our third party partner logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. You can always choose not to accept cookies through your browser's preference options, but you may not be able to use some of our services if you do not accept cookies. 

4.  Cookies

Chinatraderonline.com wants to optimize your experience by ensuring our Site’s ease of use, and that the most relevant information, promotions and offers are displayed to you while using the Chinatraderonline.com Site. A common manner in which to do this is by placing cookies on your computer. Cookies are strings of text and numbers that can identify your computer to us when you visit our site, and which may be correlated with your PII in our log files.

5.  IP Address

When you visit our site, we log standard information such as your IP address, which is a number that can be used to identify your location and Internet Service Provider, along with the URL from which you came to our site and the URLs visited on our site. A URL is the full address of a Web site page, which may or may not contain some PII about the person who is viewing it.

When we send messages to you or others, we may provide a URL link to the Chinatraderonline.com site that contains an alphanumeric identifier, which allows us to identify the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our content for that individual.

**Use of Information**

1.  Use Of Your Personally Identifiable Information by Chinatraderonline.com

Chinatraderonline.com does not sell, share or otherwise provide any PII you give to us without your express consent, which may be obtained through an opt-in or opt-out request, unless required by law, court order or as required to technically operate the service, or to complete a transaction or order. Chinatraderonline.com does reserve the right to share your PII with its parent, subsidiary or affiliated entities. We use the collected PII to contact you in connection with your transactions and other activities on the site and to operate the Chinatraderonline.com service. These types of communications may contain commercial messages, such as banner ads and special offers. Each communication we send to you, other than communications sent to you for the sole purpose of addressing a technical or operational issue regarding the Chinatraderonline.com service, will give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving further communications from us. In addition, we reserve the right to use your PII to help us provide you with personalized content, advertising, and commercial messages (collectively, "Content").

2\. Use of products Recipients’ Personally Identifiable Information by Chinatraderonline.com

Chinatraderonline.com does not use the PII of products recipients for any purpose unless required by law, court order or as required to technically operate the service, or to complete a transaction or order.

3.  Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information by Chinatraderonline.com’s Business Partners

Chinatraderonline.com will not share PII of registered users or products recipients with our Business Partners without your express consent, which may be provided by way of an opt-in or opt-out process in an email communication from Chinatraderonline.com.

PLEASE NOTE: The privacy practices of advertisers and other companies who provide services or advertising through our site are not covered by this privacy policy. Please contact those companies directly for more information about their privacy practices. If you wish to prevent those companies from setting cookies on your browser, you may set your browser to refuse cookies or to warn you before setting a cookie. Disabling cookies set by companies whose products or services are advertised on this site should not affect your ability to use this site.

4.  Use of Cookies

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. You can always choose not to accept cookies through your browser's preference options, but you may not be able to use some of our services if you do not accept cookies. 

As described in more detail above, Business Partners display ads through our service. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our Business Partners, and we do not have access to this information. Likewise, some of our Business Partners may use cookies. We do not control their use of cookies nor have access to the information contained in or related to those cookies. Please contact our Business Partners directly for more information about their privacy practices.

5.   Use Of IP Addresses

We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site and otherwise provide our service to you. IP addresses may be disclosed to Business Partners if Chinatraderonline.com believes in good faith that the law or legal process requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Chinatraderonline.com or others. In addition, our Business Partners may use information derived from your IP address, such as conducting a reverse domain name lookup, in order to provide advertisements more tailored to your interests.

**When We May Disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information**

Chinatraderonline.com may disclose your PII or the contact information of your products recipients if required to do so by law or court order. Your PII may also be disclosed if necessary in order to complete a transaction such as the fulfillment of an order or purchase placed by you. Also, certain technical processing of email messages and their content may be required to: (1) send and receive messages; (2) conform to connecting networks' technical requirements; (3) conform to the limitations of the Service; or (4) conform to other similar requirements.

It is possible that as we continue to develop our Web site and our business, Chinatraderonline.com and/or related assets might be acquired. In such a transaction, customer information may be transferred to the acquiring entity.

**Security**

This site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and integrity of the information under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information collected by the Chinatraderonline.com service in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.  

**Other Web Sites; Links**

Chinatraderonline.com contains links to other Web sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  

**Opt-Out/Correct/Delete/Deactivate**

While Chinatraderonline.com does not give you the opportunity to remove your information from our database, you may edit your registration information from your My Account page as described below. In addition, you may elect not to receive future communications from Chinatraderonline.com or to discontinue use of our service. If you are a registered user, please log in and visit you’re My Account page and uncheck the box related to sending communications to you via email. 

Chinatraderonline.com allows its users the option to change information previously provided. This may be done through the following method:

1\. Visit Chinatraderonline.com and log in;

2\. Click on the “My Account” link; and

3\. Change the relevant information.

**Changes to this Policy**

Chinatraderonline.com reserves the right to amend this privacy policy at its sole discretion. If we make any substantive changes to the policy in the future with regard to how we use your information, we will notify registered users who have agreed to receive the Chinatraderonline.com newsletter through that newsletter. For those users who have not agreed to accept the newsletter, substantive changes will be posted on the site in this location, and the date of the changes will be noted on the Web site for a period of time. Your continued use of the site after the changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes with regard to information collected in the past and in the future from you. If you do not agree to the changes, you may opt-out as described above.  

**Contacting the Web Site**

We strive to do everything we can to protect the privacy of our users. Please feel free to share any comments and concerns with us. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [notce us.](http://www.chinatraderonline.com/contactus/)

This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 15, 2005.
